My heart's YouTube has started again!
Okay, first of all, let me introduce myself.
Voice
Yes, I am the voice of Warmore Heart!
Yay!
I'm Airi Sasaki of Warmore Heart!
Yes, I'm Haruma, the MC for this show
I'm Haruma Sasaya
I'm Haruma, Haruma, Haruma.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
I'm Ayano Yajima.
Pleased to meet you.
Yay!
Yes, I'm a stone god in the rough.
LOL.
Is that how you feel?
OK.
Okay, so here's what we're going to do.
This is the project that the five of us are going to do together.
It's the other way around... not the other way around.
Harttugel.
Yay!
Huh.
Now that you know, you're in the clear.
So that's how you played the game.
I think some of you know it.Some of you may know it.
It is a game in which one player plays an emotion or situation using only words and expressions.
It's a game where you guess the other player.
I see.
By the way, is there anyone who can show what just happened? Do you have it at home?
Yes, it's unique.
I'm Nico's brother. I've never played the game.
You've never played?
Even if I had, I don't have any friends to play.
I'm sorry.
I don't have any friends either.
Shall we play?
I'll do it today.
See you later!
See you again!
And the member with the fewest points...
There will be a penalty game.
We haven't decided what the penalty game will be yet.
So, you'll have to wait and see when the results of the game are announced.
Don't miss it until the end!
Let's play the game now!
Fun!
A little focused fun!
Much more tok-tok!
Pon!
Reina, wait!
Reia, he's proposing.
Yabana, a proposal?
Reina, will you marry me, be with me, or cherish me forever?
Yahana Oh, I see.Yahana Oh, I see.
Reina, here we go. I pulled it.
Reia, here it is.
Reina, to Isshin's proposal.
Reina, three, two, one, go ahead.
Let's get married.
"Aun"?
What's an?
What do you mean by "ah"?
Did you get it? My feelings.
Yes, I did.
You got my feelings.
Wow, Loriak!
Strong! Here we go.
Me too!
Okay, then, let's hear the answers from the voices.
Wait, I'm nervous.
I'm...
Ten!
Oh!
Eeeee!
I see.
Well then, here is Annie Sasaki's answer!
Let's go!
Boom!
Oh!
G
G.
You've got two choices here.You have two choices here.
What? Is that right?
Huh?
That's not it?
It's a G.
Oh!
A G.
Let's see what Yuzuna has to say.
G.
Oh!
Yay!
If you're the only one who got this right, Perfume...
I'm getting married.
G!
Are you serious?
Really? I can already see it in your eyes.
If your eyes were serious...
But he was impressed with you, wasn't he?
The correct answer is...
Three!
G.
Oh!
Yes!
So, I recognized this one from the will face.
When I pulled this out...
Wow, it's definitely a G.
It means my acting skills were genius.
I was well-trained.I got a decent workout.
But the first one...
I loved that first breath of Sue's.
Yeah!
I get it.
Oh!
I'm so nervous!
Okay, okay, okay, I'll do my best!
So, I put on the melody
I'll do it for you, to the version for life.
Three, two, one, go!
For you!
Oh, no, this one.
I think we can afford this one.
Maybe we can afford this one.
A little more room? "Can I afford it?
I'm scared.
I'm afraid of making a mistake.
Is everyone ready with their answers?
I'm all set.
Okay, let's do this one.
I'll go first.
I chose C.
This is not good.
As expected, I chose C
I was already on it when I asked for it.I'd already asked for it, and I was already on it.
If I'm wrong on this ride, he's trying to trick me.
He's trying to trick us.
It would have been easier if I'd kept a 16-beat beat.
Like a footstep ride.
So, can you answer the question now?
Yes, let's do it! Let's go!
C
I knew it.
As expected.
Yuna Yajima got them all right, so that makes her the highest.
That's right.
I got two points last time.
Yes!
One point lead.
One lead.
Ding!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's not a sound that comes from the basics.
It's not a sound that comes from a human being.
It's a lot.
I heard a normal "keening" sound.
I thought, "Oh, that's easy.
So let's get to my key.
Keeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
Awww!
Wait, wait, wait...
The scale was going down and down and down.
What the hell?
I'm only allowed to say the key?Can I only say the key?
I'm not allowed to say anything but the keys.
Wait a minute.
A mispronunciation? This one.
Wait, one more time.
I see what you mean.
Good for you guys.
Keeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeep!
It's so different, so different.
Asami ready?
Rayo interesting.
I'm really serious about burying the weapon
Really serious wormison
He's singing
Self-destructive
I made it.
Worst of all
What the hell are you doing?
I really am.
I'm sure!
It's true! It's true!
I'm telling the truth.
All right.
That's what that was.
I'm sorry for opening up.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You're doing it for me now.
Okay, okay.
I'll say it like this.because I said so
I'm gonna...
Let's go.
G.
Oh.
With a D.
Oh, it's a D.
Oh.
Oh, no?
G. Oh.
Oh. Why? It's a G.
What? Shall we sing it?
Did you write it? I wrote it.
Oh!
It's "A"!
What?
A!
Why?
It was a lot slower.
I wanted to get that "slow key" thing going.
The second time, I changed it a little bit.
The second time, I changed it a little and made it sound like the emergency brake key.
I thought you'd understand the relationship.
But it was the funniest thing I've ever done in this game.
You're right.
I'm going to say "Diamon" now.
The different times were the funniest.The different times were the funniest.
No one is the same.
So...
Okay?
Let's hear it for Andy Sasaki.
Three, two, one, go!
Yuck.
Oh, okay.
That was pretty good, wasn't it?
That was for the whole world.
That one.
That's pretty childish.
Well, let's just get on with it, shall we?
Yes, sir.
Eng!
It's Enugu!
Don't you know "engg"?
You're the one who doesn't know "Eng"!
It's "Engg"!
I'm sorry, but you're all English!
Andy Sasaki's answer is
Quiz Words
Engg!
By the way
What is it that you wanted to do?
For the whole world
I wanted to ask you.
Let's hear it for once.
Andy Sasaki to the world!
Three, two, one, go ahead!Three, two, one, over!
Shut up!
How many hours?
I don't know! I've been in Japan.
I'd rather be on the battlefield with the boys than in a room with a bunch of guys.
Quiet!
That's what I was thinking.
That's what I used to do to all the men in the evening.
Hey, cab!
That was the scariest thing I've ever seen.
I guess this is all in my skill set, isn't it?
So, we're down to the name of the patron.
Three, two, one, go ahead.
Mono!
Normal.
Oh, wow.
Exquisite.
Is it hard?
It's too subtle.
Let's not do that.
I want to play with my what.
I don't want to play around with it.
Okay.
I already know what you mean.
I'm just getting comfortable.
I get it.
It's the last time.
Oh, really?
I'm just wondering how you guys are feeling.
If it's on your mind, I'll do it.I'll do it if you're just curious.
Then we'll do it together.
B.
I think B.
I think it's an A.
Oh, wow.
I know what you mean.
It's okay, you can split it up.
Yeah, this is...
Wouldn't it be easier if it was a "B"?
I'm gonna...
Okay, then.
I'm not afraid of punishment.
The answer's B.
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Rin-nei, a lie is an expression.
Ling Ning, you've got to be subtle about it.
Rin Ning, it's a little hard to tell if you just hear the sound.
RinNing I can tell by the look on your face.
Rin Ning, that's why you didn't see her face.
Reina, she said "thank you".
Yahana, you're lying.
Yabana, get it out.
I'm hoping for something harder.
That's for sure.
Mix it all up.
What?
What?What?
That's so funny.
I can't see it.
I can't watch it.
You're really good at this.
I'm sure they are.
Oh! It's like...
It works. I know what I'm doing wrong.
The subject is now down to the rear guard dog barking.
Three, two, one. Over.
Argh!
Oh, wow.
That's so good.
Is this me?
This is it.
Dog doesn't know the kanji a bit.
No, I know Isshin understands me.
I don't know how many words just came out!
Let's start next time!
Ready!
I'm D!
I'm D
I'm D, you're D too
Oh!
You're right.
Go!
Oh!
Oh, no.
When I was doing it, I thought it could be pink.When I did it, I thought I might be able to go pink.
I thought I might be able to go for pink, but then everyone was talking about mixing it up with Drobo
D something about mixing it up.
I wondered how to differentiate between the two.
I thought about it. When it comes to intimidation, it's a one-shot deal.
But if I put it on Drobo, it would probably be
I don't know.
I mean, what a thought!
Loose Loose Loose.
So I just thought of a mistake.
I see.
I did get lost in the "B".
That's right.
I'll take that as a sign that you're ready.
Ready?
Let's go right up to the "War of the Fretful.
Three, two, one. Over.
Whoo!
This is, this is hard.
It's hard. It's hard. It's hard.
Okay, well, I've got a good vector here.
Yeah.
Wait, so this is what I've been waiting for.
I've been waiting for this.
Okay, well, let's start with the answer.
I'll go first?
We're splitting up.
A!
Oh, yeah!
I want to be left alone!I still want to be alone!
But I'm also an A!
Ehhhhh!
I see.
By the way, my answer is B.
B?
I don't know, it was a bit...
I mean, it was a little long.
I felt a bit distant.
I felt a little distance between us.
I'm a D.
D!
Let's cheer up! I felt like I was feeling something like "Let's cheer up!
But I was torn between that and G.
I'm a G, too.
I was torn between me and G, too.
Well, I...
I got the legendary sword!
Wooooo!
Abe's ki...
It stopped.
I've got a palace to eat at home.
We have fried rice to eat at home!
yes yes yes yes
I'm not going to give up the lottery
Oh, I've got it!
He's smiling.
I'm in here.
I'm in here again.
I'll tell you.I'll tell you what.
I can't do this.
You want me to say it again?
Why don't you just make one announcement?
Raw barley, raw rice, raw eggs.
I can say it.
It's so funny.
Say it.
It's so funny!
You can say it in the first place.
Say it three times together.
Here we go.
You're a fast pusher, aren't you?
Did you say it already?
Too fast.
Too soon.
Sorry, I cut you off.
Now, to the genre of raw oats, raw rice, raw eggs...
Three, two, one, go!
Raw barley, raw rice, raw egg.
What?
Oh!
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, this?
You're kidding me.
No, it's pretty hard.
I thought it was pretty good.
Oh, man, once a guy's made up his mind...
I don't have two.I don't have two pens.
I'll put the pen down.
I'm putting the pen down.
Oops.
Is everyone in order?
We're ready.
Let's get it all out at once, this time.
Let's do it all at once.
C.
Why C?
Why, the ocean?
Well, it's not an S, so...
I'm getting it out of here.
What's that?
It's normal.
C, no.
C, C, C.
That's too much.
Okay, let's get right to it.
The answer is
Durrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
C.
S.
Really?
I swear.
That was awkward.
No, you said it pretty well.
No, I could say
I could tell.
Wow, seriously?Wow, seriously?
But I'll get right to it.
I'll get right to it.
I'll get to the subject, but...
Huh.
Ha-ha-ha!
The way they all laughed.
I was a window washer.
Window washers.
That was pretty scary.
That's not the phrase this time.
What?
It's a body movement.
There's movement in this game?
Enclosed Mind Pose
Enclosed Heart Pose
What a fun game!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Interesting!
That's funny.
Okay, I'll morph.
Yeah, okay.
Wait a minute.
I'm a little embarrassed.
This is cute.
Cute.
Oh, no.
This is new.That's new.
No, it's kind of amazing.
What a game with so much potential!
Let's play it all at once!
Let's do it all at once!
E F.
No way.
H
Well...
I was torn between E, F, and H.
E is for the old
I don't know what a hero is.
I don't know anything about the old days.
I see.
You don't see it.
It was pretty simple.
I thought it was that.
I thought it was innovative.
I kind of imagined it.
I see.
I thought it was a little uncool.
This...
This one.
If this were...
If it was D...
Please.
Let's go a little forward.
Oh, that's good.
It's a D.
Uh...Oh, my God.
That's so bad!
But I really thought it was D.
Seriously.
Because, you know, it has to be simple.
Because the other ones are so peculiar.
No, no, if it's a D, I thought they'd add something quirky.
Something cool about it.
On the contrary.
I thought he'd put in something like this.
It's a little too simple.
But then I'd be confused if it wasn't cool.
Today's my day.
Oh my God, it's so loud!
Subscribe to my channel!
And now, rise and shine... until you wake up.
321, please.
Get up!
This might be hard.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think I'm getting the hang of this.
I got it.
I got a moment's worth of thoughts.
I'm kind of... I'm kind of behind your back, but...
Here we go.
Let's go!
D!
We split up.
Koyu-san's on his way to Yukiya.Koyu-san up to Yukiya-san
As expected, Satoyaju-san is in D, here in D
Tanoha-san is here in G
Get angry!
Hey!
On G.
The correct answer is
D.
At Shun Kawashima's training camp.
I was confused at first.
When I first heard "at the camp"...
Surprisingly, it's easy to understand in this case.
If you do it the normal way...
But...
I wanted to include something here.
So I'm going to yell one word.
How do you think people would feel if you just did that?
I wonder how they'll feel.
I really want them to wake up.
I thought it would take that kind of tension.
I wrote the position
But you're number one, so...
How do you feel about it?
It was fun, so I'm OK with it.
Now I'd like to learn Haruma's punishment game
I'd like to learn Haruma's game.
Punishment games?
At the next pre-event
I will receive 1000% priceI'll take 1000% price.
I'm punishing you again today.
Punishment.
It's a penalty game.
I have to feel like I'm being punished more than usual.
Okay, then.
I'll make it one chorus.
I really want you to play it.
Don't say 1,000, but 10,000,000,000,000,000.
Sure.
Okay, I'll do that.
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
Let's review.
Just a quick recap.
We'll go in SE.
Next free show, we'll go in SE.
Enter in SE for the event split.
One half 1000% or more AL4U
Okay, let's see...
Everyone watching this.
One of these days, at the next free event.
I'll probably announce it on Twitter or something.
So please come then!
That's why
This video will be out
At the next free show
I will be playing the penalty game.
Please come to that free live show, too!
So, that's it.That's all for now.
That's all for One Love One Heart
It was a game of hearts!
Bye bye!
by H.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
I can't take it anymore.
No more.